James E. McDonald papers, (1904-1997)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup I: UFO Research Files, 1904-1971
  - Series 2: Project Blue Book, 1947-1968
    - July 4, 1947: Mt. Jefferson, Washington. (Box 15)
    - July 4, 1947: Boise, Idaho. (Box 15)
    - July 4, 1947: Portland, Oregon. (Box 15)
    - July 6, 1947: Clay Center, Kansas. (Box 15)
    - July 6, 1947: Fairfield Suisun AFB, Calif. (Box 15)
    - July 7, 1947: Hickam Village, Havana. (Box 15)
    - July 7, 1947: Shreveport, Louisiana. (Box 15)
    - July 7-8, 1947: Muroc AFB, Calif. (Box 15)
    - July 9, 1947: Boise-Meridian, Idaho. (Box 15)
    - July 29, 1947: Canyon Ferry, New York. (Box 15)
    - July 29, 1947: Hamilton Field, California. (Box 15)
    - July 11, 1947: Elmendorf AFB, Anchor, Alaska. (Box 15)
    - August 4, 1947: NW of Bethel, Alaska. (Box 15)
    - August 4, 1947: Boston, Mass. (Box 15)
    - August 13, 1947: Salmon Dam, Idaho. (Box 15)
    - August 13, 1947: Twin Falls, Idaho. (Box 15)
    - August 14, 1947: 5 miles S. of Placerville, Calif. (Box 15)
    - August 15-20, 1947: Rapid City AFB, Weaver, South Dakota. (Box 15)
    - August 19, 1947: Twin Falls, Idaho. (Box 15)
    - August (Late) 1947: Holloman AFB, New Mexico. (Box 15)
    - September 3, 1947: Oswego, Oregon. (Box 15)
    - September 8, 1947: Logan, Utah. (Box 15)
    - September 12, 1947: Midway Island to Oahu, Beyond Necker I. (Box 15)
    - September 17, 1947: Ft. Richardson, Alaska. (Box 15)
    - October 8/9, 1947: Las Vegas, Nevada. (Box 15)
    - October 14, 1947: Phoenix, Arizona. (Box 15)
    - October 20, 1947: Xenia, Ohio. (Box 15)
    - October 20, 1947: Dayton, Ohio. (Box 15)
    - November 2, 1947: Anderson Rd., Houston, Texas. (Box 15)
    - November 12, 1947: 40 miles N. of Cape Blanco, Oregon. (Box 15)
    - Mid-December 1947: Northern Arizona. (Box 15)
    - December 30, 1947: 30 miles W. Lovelock, Nevada. (Box 15)
    - January 10, 1948: Wildwood, NJ. (Box 15)
    - April 1, 1948: Philippine Islands. (Box 15)
    - April 8, 1948: Asley, Ohio. (Box 15)
    - April 9, 1948: Montgomery, Alabama. (Box 15)
    - April 11, 1948: Alton, Ill. (Box 15)
    - April 18, 1948: North Atlantic 62 degrees N, 33 degrees. (Box 15)
    - April 18, 1948: North Atlantic. (Box 15)
    - April 18, 1948: Fairbanks, Alaska. (Box 15)
    - April 19, 1948: Greenville AFB, S.C. (Box 15)
    - April 30, 1948: Anacostia NAS, W. D.C. (Box 15)
    - May 5, 1948: Adapasari, Turkey. (Box 15)
    - May 6, 1948: Wake Island. (Box 15)
    - May 7, 1948: Memphis, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - May 31, 1948: Wilmington, N.C. (Box 15)
    - June 1948: Galveston, Texas. (Box 15)
    - June 20, 1948: Scott AFB, Ill. (Box 15)
    - June 29, 1948: Union Town, PA. (Box 15)
    - June 30, 1948: S. Knoxville, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - June 30, 1948: Hecla, So. Dakota. (Box 15)
    - July 4, 1948: Dravesburg, PA. (Box 15)
    - July 8, 1948: McDeesport, PA. (Box 15)
    - July 9, 1948: Fielding Lake, Wash. (Box 15)
    - July 21, 1948: Van Nuys, Calif. (Box 15)
    - July 24, 1948: Altoona, PA. (Box 15)
    - July 26, 1948: Chamblee, Georgia. (Box 15)
    - July 31, 1948: Indianapolis, Indiana. (Box 15)
    - Summer 1948: Bedford, VA. (Box 15)
    - July, August 1948: Marian, VA. (Box 15)
    - August 2, 1948: Columbus, OH. (Box 15)
    - August 3, 1948: Moscow, USSR. (Box 15)
    - August 4, 1948: North Powder, Oregon. (Box 15)
    - August 11, 1948: Hamel, Minn. (Box 15)
    - August 29, 1948: Maplewood, OH. (Box 15)
    - September 18, 1948: San Simeon, Calif. (Box 15)
    - September 22, 1948: Turner AFB, Albany, GA. (Box 15)
    - September 23, 1948: Santa Fe, N.M. (Box 15)
    - September 23, 1948: San Pablo, Calif. (Box 15)
    - October 11, 1948: Neubiberg AFB, Munich, Germany. (Box 15)
    - October 13, 1948: South Bend, Indiana. (Box 15)
    - October 17, 1948: Crescent City, Calif. (Box 15)
    - October 19, 1948: Honolulu, Hawaii. (Box 15)
    - October 24, 1948: 10 miles SW of Junction City, Kansas. (Box 15)
    - October 24, 1948: Fargo, ND. (Box 15)
    - October 24, 1948: Phoenix, Arizona. (Box 15)
    - October 27, 1948: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 15)
    - October 30, 1948: Gray's Harbor, Mich. (Box 15)
    - October 31, 1948: Goose Bay, Labrador. (Box 15)
    - October 31, 1948: Azores Isles. (Box 15)
    - Fall, 1948:Martha's Vineyard, Mass. (Box 15)
    - November 3-4, 1948: 10 mi. E. Vaughn, NM. (Box 15)
    - November 6, 1948: Wakkana, Japan. (Box 15)
    - November 12, 1948: Clark AFB, Philippines. (Box 15)
    - November 17, 1948: Peace River, Alberta, Canada. (Box 15)
    - November 18, 1948: Andrews AFB, MD. (Box 15)
    - November 23, 1948: Fursten-Feldbruck, Germany. (Box 15)
    - November 26, 1948: Washington & Oregon. (Box 15)
    - December 3, 1948: Dayton, OH. (Box 15)
    - December 3, 1948: Fairfield-Suisun AFB, Calif. (Box 15)
    - December 6-9, 1948: Kirtland AFB, N.M. (Box 15)
    - December 8, 1948: Chanute AFB, Ill. (Box 15)
    - December 9, 1948: Pittsburgh, PA. (Box 15)
    - December 17, 1948: Ambridge, PA. (Box 15)
    - December 30, 1948: Sweden. (Box 15)
    - January 1, 1949: Jackson, Miss. (Box 15)
    - January 4, 1949: Hickam Field, Hawaii. (Box 15)
    - January 6, 1949: Los Alamos, NM. (Box 15)
    - March 17, 1949: Camp Hood, TX. (Box 15)
    - March 18, 1949: Camp Hood, TX. (Box 15)
    - April 24, 1949: Arrey, NM. (Box 15)
    - April 28, 1949: Tucson, AZ. (Box 15)
    - May 5, 1949: Ft. Bliss, TX. (Box 15)
    - May 27, 1949: So. Oregon. (Box 15)
    - July 30, 1949: Mt. Hood, Oregon. (Box 15)
    - November 23, 1949: Mt. Palomar, Calif. (Box 15)
    - January 12, 1950: 2400 N. - 8520 W. Gulf of Mexico. (Box 15)
    - February 5, 1950: Teaticket, Mass. (Box 15)
    - February 25, 1950: Los Alamos, NM. (Box 15)
    - March 8, 1950: Vandalia, OH. (Box 15)
    - March 9, 1950: Selfridge AFB, Mich. (Box 15)
    - March 22, 1950: Little Rock, Ark. (Box 15)
    - March 27, 1950: Motubu Peninsula, Okinawa. (Box 15)
    - March 30, 1950: Marrowbore Lake, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - April 1950: Kokomo, Ind. (Box 15)
    - May 19, 1950: Honshu, Japan. (Box 15)
    - May 24, 1950: Holloman AFB, NM. (Box 15)
    - June 27, 1950: Texarkana, TX. (Box 15)
    - August 24, 1950: Bermuda. (Box 15)
    - August 30, 1950: Holloman AFB. (Box 15)
    - September 8, 1950: Germany. (Box 15)
    - September 21, 1950: Provincetown, Mass. (Box 15)
    - October 12, 1950: Knoxville, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - November 10, 1950: South Ruislip, England. (Box 15)
    - November 14-15, 1950: Key West, Fla. (Box 15)
    - November 23, 1950: Maxwell AFB, Alabama. (Box 15)
    - November 29-30, 1950: Knoxville, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - December 18, 1950: Oak Ridge, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - December 19, 1950: 10 minutes NW Bulkang, Alaska. (Box 15)
    - December 27, 1950: Lakehurst, NJ. (Box 15)
    - January 16, 1951: Artesia, NM. (Box 15)
    - January 20, 1951: Sioux City, Iowa. (Box 15)
    - January 21, 1951: Oak Ridge, Tenn. (Box 15)
    - January 24, 1951: Westover AFB, Mass. (Box 15)
    - February 10, 1951: 49.50 N, 50.03 W, Atlantic. (Box 15)
    - March 13, 1951: McClellan AFB, Calif. (Box 15)
    - July 14, 1951 & July 9, 1951: Holloman AFB, NM. (Box 15)
    - July 30, 1951: Selfridge AFB, Mich. (Box 15)
    - August 26, 1951: Larson AFB, Washington. (Box 15)
    - August 31, 1951: Matador, TX. (Box 15)
    - September 10-11, 1951: Ft. Monmouth. (Box 15)
    - September 13, 1951: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 15)
    - September 18, 1951: Michigan, Wisc. (Box 15)
    - September 23, 1951: Long Beach, Calif. (Box 15)
    - October 3, 1951: Kadena AFB, Okinawa. (Box 16)
    - October 18, 1951: Yellow Sea. (Box 16)
    - October 21, 1951: Battle Creek, Mich. (Box 16)
    - October 22, 1951: No. Truro, Mass. (Box 16)
    - December 22, 1951: Columbus, Ohio. (Box 16)
    - January 21, 1952: Mitchel AFB, NY. (Box 16)
    - January 22, 1952: Nanana, Alaska. (Box 16)
    - January 29, 1952: Korea. (Box 16)
    - February 13, 1952: Granite City, Ill. (Box 16)
    - February 16, 1952: Korea. (Box 16)
    - February 24, 1952: No. Korea. (Box 16)
    - March 24, 1952: Pt. Conception, Calif. (Box 16)
    - March 26, 1952: Ft. Stockton, Texas. (Box 16)
    - March 29, 1952: Misawa, Japan. (Box 16)
    - April 5, 1952: Glendale, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - April 5, 1952: Duncanville, Texas. (Box 16)
    - April 6, 1952: Miller-Graughan AFB, Temple, Texas. (Box 16)
    - April 9, 1952: Shreveport La. (Box 16)
    - April 13, 1952: Moriarity, N M. (Box 16)
    - April 14, 1952: Memphis, Tenn. (Box 16)
    - April 16, 1952: Shreveport, La. (Box 16)
    - April 17 & 18, 1952: Yuma, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - April 18, 1952: Japan. (Box 16)
    - April 27, 1952: Yuma, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - April 30, 1952: Moriarity, NM. (Box 16)
    - May 1, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 8, 1952: Atlantic Ocean. (Box 16)
    - May 9, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 9, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 9, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 9, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 10, 1952: Albuquerque, NM. (Box 16)
    - May 11, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 11, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 14, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 20, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 13, 1952: George AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - May 15, 1952: Washington, D.C. (Box 16)
    - May 25, 1952: Randolph AFB, Texas. (Box 16)
    - May 25, 1952: Tierra Amarilla, NM. (Box 16)
    - May 26, 1952: North Korea. (Box 16)
    - June 12, 1952: Marrakech, Morocco. (Box 16)
    - June 18, 1952: March AFB, Calif. (Box 16)
    - June 19, 1952: Yuma, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - June 19, 1952: George AB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - June 21, 1952: Marxville, Tenn. (Box 16)
    - July 1, 1952: Ft. Monmouth, N J. (Box 16)
    - July 10, 1952: Quantico, Va. (Box 16)
    - July 13, 1952: Washington, D.C. (Box 16)
    - July 13, 1952: Kirksville, MD. (Box 16)
    - July 16, 1952: Hampton Roads, Va. (Box 16)
    - July 19, 1952: Washington, D.C. (Box 16)
    - July 19-20 & July 26-27, 1952: Washington, D.C. (Box 16)
    - July 21, 1952: Dobbins AFB, Ga. (Box 16)
    - July 22, 1952: Boston, Mass. (Box 16)
    - July 23, 1952: Jamestown, Rhode Island. (Box 16)
    - July 23, 1952: McDill AFB, Fla. (Box 16)
    - July 24, 1952: Carson Sink, Nev. (Box 16)
    - July 23, 1952: Kirtland AFB, NM. (Box 16)
    - March 23, 1952: Yakima, Wash. (Box 16)
    - July 28, 1952: McGuire AFB, NJ. (Box 16)
    - July 29, 1952: Port Huron, Mich. (Box 16)
    - July 29, 1952: Los Alamos, NM. (Box 16)
    - July 29, 1952: Miami, Fla. (Box 16)
    - August 4, 1952: Phoenix, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - August 4, 1952: Phoenix, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - September 2, 1952: Tokyo, Japan. (Box 16)
    - September 24, 1952: Guantanamo Bay, Cuba. (Box 16)
    - September 28, 1952: Tsu Shima, Japan. (Box 16)
    - September 28, 1952: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - October 15, 1952: Ashiya, Japan. (Box 16)
    - November 8, 1952: Tierra Amarilla, NM. (Box 16)
    - November 18, 1952: Glasgow, Mont. (Box 16)
    - November 15, 1952: Wichita, Kan. (Box 16)
    - November 25, 1952: White Sands, NM. (Box 16)
    - November 26, 1952: Goose Bay, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - November 30, 1952: Washington, D.C. (Box 16)
    - December 4, 1952: Colorado Springs, Colo. (Box 16)
    - December 4, 1952: Congares AFB, South Dakota. (Box 16)
    - December 6, 1952: Gulf of Mexico. (Box 16)
    - December 6, 1952: Angoon, Alaska. (Box 16)
    - December 10, 1952: Pope AFB, SC. (Box 16)
    - December 15, 1952: Goose AB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - December 15, 1952: Honshu, Japan. (Box 16)
    - December 24, 1952: Camp Carson, Colo. (Box 16)
    - December 29, 1952: Japan. (Box 16)
    - December 29, 1952: Hokkaido Island, Japan. (Box 16)
    - January 1, 1953: Craig, Mont. (Box 16)
    - January 6, 1953: Dallas area, Texas. (Box 16)
    - January 9, 1953: Misawa, Japan. (Box 16)
    - January 10, 1953: Sonoma, Calif. (Box 16)
    - January 23, 1953: Bergstrom AFB, Texas. (Box 16)
    - January 28, 1953: Moody AFB. (Box 16)
    - Turner AFB, Ga.. (Box 16)
    - February (deleted), 1953: Finland, Minn. (Box 16)
    - February 3, 1953: Keflavik Airport, Iceland. (Box 16)
    - February 4, 1953: Yuma, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - February 6, 1953: Rosalia, Wash. (Box 16)
    - February 7, 1953: Okinawa, Japan. (Box 16)
    - February 10, 1953: Misawa, Japan. (Box 16)
    - February 16, 1953: Raimer, Ala. (Box 16)
    - February 17, 1953: Port Austin, Mich. (Box 16)
    - February 25, 1953: Charleston, W. Va. (Box 16)
    - February 27, 1953: Great Falls AFB, Mont. (Box 16)
    - March 3, 1953: Luke AFB, Arizona. (Box 16)
    - March 5, 1953: Congares AFB & Shaw AFB, S.C. (Box 16)
    - March 14, 1053: Sea of Japan. (Box 16)
    - March 8, 1953: Ashiya AFB, Kyushu, Japan. (Box 16)
    - March 20, 1953: Pork Chop Hill, Korea. (Box 16)
    - March 23, 1953: Pasadena, Texas. (Box 16)
    - March 25, 1953: San Antonio, Texas. (Box 16)
    - March 25, 1953: Rabat, Morocco. (Box 16)
    - March 29, 1953: Spooner, Wisc. (Box 16)
    - March 31, 1953: Honshu, Japan. (Box 16)
    - April 12, 1953: Sweetwater, Nev. (Box 16)
    - April 14, 19, 21, 23, 1953: Manchuria. (Box 16)
    - April 15, 1953: Tucson, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - April 19, 1953: Calumet, Mich. Lake Superior area. (Box 16)
    - May 1, 1953: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - May 2, 1953: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - May 12, 1953: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - June 11, 1953: Goose AFB, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - June 16, 1953: San Antonio, Texas. (Box 16)
    - June 18, 1953: Iwo Jima. (Box 16)
    - June 26, 1953: Iwo Jima. (Box 16)
    - July 3, 1953: Tipp City, Ohio. (Box 16)
    - July 20, 1953: Offutt AFB, Neb. (Box 16)
    - August 5, 1953: Rapid City, So. Dakota. (Box 16)
    - August 23, 1953: Port Moresby New Guinea. (Box 16)
    - September 28, 1953: Palmdale, Calif. (Box 16)
    - October 13, 1953: Offutt AFB, Neb. (Box 16)
    - October 16, 1953: Presque Isle, Maine. (Box 16)
    - December 3, 1953: North Truro, Mass. (Box 16)
    - December 3, 1953: Holloman AFB, NM. (Box 16)
    - December 16, 1953: Mediterranean. (Box 16)
    - January 14, 1954: Kelly AFB, Texas. (Box 16)
    - March 5-7, 1954: Nouasseur, French Morocco. (Box 16)
    - March 11-12, 1954: Pittsburgh, Pa.. (Box 16)
    - May 14, 1954: Norfolk, England. (Box 16)
    - June 30, 1954: Mobile, Ala. (Box 16)
    - July 3, 1954: Bermuda. (Box 16)
    - July 27, 1954: Pepperell AFB, Newfoundland. (Box 16)
    - July 29, 1954: Korea. (Box 16)
    - October 5, 1954: Houston, Texas. (Box 16)
    - October 23, 1954: Tinker AFB, Okla. (Box 16)
    - November 16, 1954: New Orleans, La. (Box 16)
    - December 2, 1954: Spanish Morocco. (Box 16)
    - December 23, 1954: Nogales, Ariz. (Box 16)
    - March 20, 1955: Tokyo, Japan. (Box 16)
    - March 29, 1955: Soledad & Sonoma, Calif. (Box 16)
    - April 28, 1955: Dahlgren, Va. (Box 16)
    - May 13, 1955: Duluth, Minn. (Box 16)
    - July 1, 1955: China Lake, Calif. (Box 16)
    - July 5, 1955: Newfoundland, Canada. (Box 16)
    - July-August 1955: Mulberry Corners, Ohio. (Box 16)
    - August 25, 1955: Forland, Missouri. (Box 16)
    - October 19, 1955: Knoxville, Texas. (Box 16)
    - October 20, 1955: Minneapolis, Minn.. (Box 16)
    - November 17, 1955: St. Louis, Missouri. (Box 16)
    - December 6, 1955: Marianna, Fla.. (Box 16)
    - December 13, 1955: Caddo Lake, La.. (Box 16)
    - December 17, 1955: Laguna, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - January 11, 1956: Wurtsmith AFB, Mich.. (Box 16)
    - January 24, 1956: Wheelus AFB, Morocco. (Box 16)
    - January 24, 1956: Wheelus AFB, Morocco. (Box 16)
    - February 2, 9, 21, 1956: Camp Irwin, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - February 7, 1956: Kessler AFB, Miss.. (Box 16)
    - February 12, 1956: Goose Bay, Labrador. (Box 16)
    - March 3, 1956: Spokane, Wash.. (Box 16)
    - April 8, 1956: A/V Sighting between Schenectady & Oswego, NY. (Box 16)
    - May 8, 1956: Aliquippa, Pa.. (Box 16)
    - May 22, 1956: 50 mi. NW of Monroe, La.. (Box 16)
    - June 6, 1956: Banning, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - June 29, 1956: Scattered points/So. Calif., LA to San Diego. (Box 16)
    - July 6, 1956: Euclid, Ohio. (Box 16)
    - July 17, 1956: Westover AFB, Mass.. (Box 16)
    - August 10-11, 1956: Dallas, Texas. (Box 16)
    - August 17, 1956: SSW Spragueville, Maine. (Box 16)
    - August 20, 1956: North Bend, Ore.. (Box 16)
    - August 22, 1956: Bornholm, Denmark. (Box 16)
    - October 9, 1956: Essex, England. (Box 16)
    - October 18, 1956: Wheelus AB, Libya. (Box 16)
    - November 4, 1956: Point Arena, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - November 11-12, 1956: El Toro, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - December 17, 1956: Itazuke, AB, Japan. (Box 16)
    - February 7, 1957: Las Cruces, NM. (Box 16)
    - February 13, 1957: Marrero, La.. (Box 16)
    - February 13, 1957: Lincoln AFB, Neb.. (Box 16)
    - February 13, 1957: Tierra Amarilla, NM. (Box 16)
    - February 27, 1957: Castle AFB, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - February 27, 1957: Castle AFB, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - March 22, 1957: Point Mugu, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - March 23, 1957: Oxnard, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - May 29, 1957: Houma, La.. (Box 16)
    - May 30, 1957: Detroit, Mich.. (Box 16)
    - June 3, 1957: Shreveport, La.. (Box 16)
    - June 14, 1957: McChord AFB, Wash.. (Box 16)
    - July 16, 1957: Las Vegas, Nev.. (Box 16)
    - July 18, 1957: Mt. Lemmon AFB, Tucson, Ariz.. (Box 16)
    - August 3, 1957: Northern California. (Box 16)
    - August 22-23, 1957: Cambria AFS, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - August 22-23, 1957: Cambria AFS, Calif.. (Box 16)
    - August 27, 1957: Dry Tortugas, Fla.. (Box 16)
    - September 12, 1957: Tulsa, Okla.. (Box 16)
    - September 20, 1957: Mantauk, N.Y. Benton, Penn.. (Box 16)
    - October 19, 1957: Mildenhall, England. (Box 16)
    - October 22, 1957: Wiesbaden, Ga.. (Box 16)
    - November 2, 1957: Canadian, Texas. (Box 17)
    - November 3, 1957: White Sands, NM. (Box 17)
    - November 4, 1957: Oro Grande, NM. (Box 17)
    - November 5, 1957: Long Beach Airport, Calif. (Box 17)
    - November 5, 1957: Eglin AFB, Fla.. (Box 17)
    - November 6, 1957: Montsville, Ohio. (Box 17)
    - November 6, 1957: Kagohima, Japan. (Box 17)
    - November 6, 1957: Laredo AFB, Texas. (Box 17)
    - November 6, 1957: Whitman AFB, Missouri. (Box 17)
    - November 7, 1957: Harlingen AFB, Texas. (Box 17)
    - November 14, 1957: Rothwesten, Germany. (Box 17)
    - November 21, 1957: Houm, Alabama. (Box 17)
    - November 23, 1957: Joliet, Ill.. (Box 17)
    - November 25, 1957: Eglin AFB, Fla.. (Box 17)
    - November 26, 1957: West Mesa AFB, NM. (Box 17)
    - November 30, 1957: Minot, No. Dakota. (Box 17)
    - December 11, 1957: Guthrie, W. Va.& Parkersburg, W. Va.. (Box 17)
    - December 11, 1957: Lake City AFS, Tenn.. (Box 17)
    - December 12-15, 1957: Misawa Chitose-Hokkaido, Japan. (Box 17)
    - December 19, 1957: Pepperrell AFB, Newfoundland. (Box 17)
    - December 23, 1957: Sea of Japan. (Box 17)
    - January 4, 1958: SW Libya. (Box 17)
    - January 9, 1958: Biggs AFB, El Paso, Texas. (Box 17)
    - January 11, 1958: Bering Sea Area. (Box 17)
    - January 14, 1958: Bering Sea. (Box 17)
    - February 13, 1958: W. of Wake Island. (Box 17)
    - February 25, 1958: Glenwood, Newfoundland. (Box 17)
    - February 25, 1958: Gander AFB, Newfoundland. (Box 17)
    - May 3, 1958, May 28, 1958 Flagstaff, Ariz. & Templehof, Germany. (Box 17)
    - June 14, 1958, August 4, 1958: Pueblo, Colo. & Malstrom AFB, Montana. (Box 17)
    - August 11, 1958: Osel Island & Gulf of Finland. (Box 17)
    - August 17, 1958: Warren, Mich.. (Box 17)
    - August 30, 1958: Gray AFB, Killeen, Texas. (Box 17)
    - September 1, 1958: Wheelus AFB, Tripoli, Libya. (Box 17)
    - September 5, 1958: 19.03 N, 68.56 W, Atlantic.b (Box 17)
    - September 7, 1958:Miles City AFS, Ellsworth AFB, SD, 12 mi. S of Minot, ND. (Box 17)
    - September 14, 1958: Wheelus AFB, Libya. (Box 17)
    - September 21, 1958: Sheffield Lake, Ohio. (Box 17)
    - September 23, 1958: Kindley AFB, Bermuda. (Box 17)
    - October 11, 1958: Laredo, Texas. (Box 17)
    - November 13, 1958: Troy Peak & Tonopah Airport, Nev.. (Box 17)
    - November 19, 1958: Montauk AFB, NY. (Box 17)
    - March 10, 1959: Grand Bahama Island, West Indies. (Box 17)
    - March 12, 1959: Duluth, Finland, Minn.. (Box 17)
    - March 13, 1959: Duluth, Minn.. (Box 17)
    - March 13, 1959: Duluth, Minn.. (Box 17)
    - March 14, 1959: Ellsworth AFB, So. Dakota. (Box 17)
    - March 22, 1959: Ann Arbor, Mich.. (Box 17)
    - March 25, 1959: No. Montana. (Box 17)
    - March 26 or 27, 1959: Corsica, Penn.. (Box 17)
    - April 13, 1959: Antigo & Madison, Wisc.. (Box 17)
    - May 2, 1959: Pease AFB, N.H.. (Box 17)
    - May 13, 1959: Offut AFB, Nebraska. (Box 17)
    - May 14, 1959: Philadelphia, Penn.. (Box 17)
    - May 18, 1959: Greenbush, Kansas. (Box 17)
    - May 21, 1959: 8 mi. E of Rapid City, So. Dakota. (Box 17)
    - June 3, 1959: Genoa, Italy. (Box 17)
    - June 9, 1959: Manassas, Roanoke, Va.. (Box 17)
    - June 16, 1959: WSE of Meridian, Miss.. (Box 17)
    - June 18, 1959: 33.05 N, 134 W, Pacific. (Box 17)
    - June 18, 1959: Forest Park, Ill.. (Box 17)
    - June 18, 1959: Stephenson, Mich, Sault Ste. Marie. (Box 17)
    - June 18, 1959: Enon, Ohio. (Box 17)
    - June 18, 1959: Lyons, Colo.. (Box 17)
    - June 18, 1959: Eamonton, Alberta, Canada. (Box 17)
    - June 21, 1959: South of Macao, China. (Box 17)
    - June 25, 1959: South of Taegu, Korea. (Box 17)
    - June 27, 1959: Dunville, Va.. (Box 17)
    - June 30, 1959: Patuxent River NAS, Maryland. (Box 17)
    - July 3, 1959: Needles, Calif.. (Box 17)
    - July 9, 1959: Bahamas. (Box 17)
    - July 11, 1959: North Pacific, Hawaii. (Box 17)
    - July 14, 1959: New Delhi, India. (Box 17)
    - July 25, 1958: Irendequoit, NY. (Box 17)
    - July 28, 1959: Corpus Christi, Texas. (Box 17)
    - July 28, 1959: East of Florida. (Box 17)
    - August 2, 1959: Washington, DC. (Box 17)
    - August 3, 1959: Silver Springs, Maryland. (Box 17)
    - August 16, 1959: Macon and Forsyth, Ga.. (Box 17)
    - August 19, 1959: 80 mi East of U.S.. (Box 17)
    - August 28, 1959: Charlotte Island., Canada. (Box 17)
    - September 5, 1959: Haha, Okinawa. (Box 17)
    - September 7, 1959: Wallingford, Ky.. (Box 17)
    - September 10, 1959: Camp Kinser, Okinawa. (Box 17)
    - September 13, 1959: Gills Rock, Wisc.. (Box 17)
    - September 13, 1959: Bunker Hill AFB, Ind.. (Box 17)
    - September 15, 1959: Kadena, Okinawa. (Box 17)
    - September 20, 1961: Lincoln, NH. (Box 17)
    - September 24, 1959: Redmond, Ore.. (Box 17)
    - October 2, 1959: Seattle, Wash.. (Box 17)
    - October 4, 1959: Philippines. (Box 17)
    - October 6, 1959: Lincoln, Nebr.. (Box 17)
    - October 12, 1959: Washington, Ga.. (Box 17)
    - October 19, 1959: North of Langley AFB, Va.. (Box 17)
    - October 21, 1959: Warsaw, NY. (Box 17)
    - October 22-23, 1959: Loring AFB, Maine area. (Box 17)
    - October 26, 1959: Toccoa, Ga.. (Box 17)
    - November 5, 1959: Montauk AFS: Long Island, NY. (Box 17)
    - December 18, 1959: Southern Victoria Island, Canada. (Box 17)
    - December 23, 1959: West of Albuquerque, NM. (Box 17)
    - May 7, 1960: Canada, Montana, North Dakota. (Box 17)
    - June 4, 1960: Pacific Ocean. (Box 17)
    - September 10, 1960: Ridgecrest, Calif.. (Box 17)
    - September 10, 1960: Ridgecrest, Calif.. (Box 17)
    - September 19, 1960: Susanville, Calif.. (Box 17)
    - September 20, 1960:Kirksville AFS, Missouri. (Box 17)
    - September 20, 1960: SE of Farmington, NM. (Box 17)
    - September 25, 1960: Midway Isles. (Box 17)
    - September 28, 1960: Kirksville, Missouri. (Box 17)
    - January 10, 1961: 19.48 N. 73.40 W. Atlantic. (Box 17)
    - January 10. 1961: Wichita Falls, Kansas. (Box 17)